http://www.customercare.co/privacy.html

Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy applies to the following "SITES",
or individually a "SITE", currently including:
ADDISONSTJAMES.COM, AMANDAAMORE.COM, ANGIEXXX.COM, BANGINGWHITEY.COM, BIOHAZARDBITCHES.COM, CAMGIRLMINNIE.COM, CUMCRAZYWIFE.COM, CUMHOGS.COM, CUTELATINA.COM, CRYGASM.COM, DITZIDANI.COM, EMBRIANNA.COM, GLAMOURSMOKERS.COM, INKEDANDI.COM, KORA-KRYK.COM, LACTALIA.COM, MALINA-MAY.COM, MINNIESTCLAIRE.COM, MONTREALDREAM.COM, NASTYADAMEVE.COM, NUDENADIA.COM, PREGNANTKRISTI.COM, SESKA.COM, SMOKINGMINA.COM, SUICIDESCARLETT.COM, XXXMINA.COM, HORNYLESBIANGFS.COM, ILOVEBLACKGIRLS.COM, REALTEENS.COM, SANDIEGOLATINAS.COM, WAVEHOS.COM, CALITEENS.COM, INSANECOEDS.COM, UNLIMITEDACCESSPASS.COM, LESBIANASSAULT.COM, LOUISAMAY.COM, PRINCESSRIO.COM, BROOKLITTLE.COM, JESSICACUTE.COM, MEGANSWEETS.COM, ILOVEBITTIES.COM, BOOBIEPASS.COM, VICTORIASUMMERS.COM, CHLOELOVETTE.COM, TEENAMBITIONS.COM, TEENCASTINGS.COM, STACEYLACEY.COM, STACEYROCKS.COM, CUNTMUNCHERS.COM, BRATSLUTS.COM, PORNMICROS.COM, GIRLSIESPASS.COM, CUTIETEASE.COM, ALICIADREAMS.COM, EMILYSTAR.COM, KAYLEEKISS.COM, LILYSWEET.COM, LISADUKES.COM, LUCYLUST.COM, MADISONBANGS.COM, ALEXADOLL.COM, CHLOECOED.COM, NAOMITEEN.COM, CARLITEEN.COM, MISSBRACES.COM, SASHABANGS.COM, NATALIESPANKS.COM, LACEYSWEET.COM, CLAIREPETITE.COM, RUBYDESIRES.COM, VONREBEL.COM, KELLYCANE.COM, CANDYSUMMERS.COM, MARIASPANKS.COM, GEMMALITTLE.COM, MICHATEEN.COM, PRINCESSBRATTY.COM, SOPHIEBANKS.COM, SOPHIECOCKS.CO.UK, VICKYHEART.COM, GOLDENPASSIONS.COM, INESCAPABLEBONDAGE.COM, CBTANDBALLBUSTING.COM, FEMDOMFOOTFETISH.COM, RYANNEREDD.COM,SMUTTYPASS.COM, SMUTTYSPASS.COM, CUMCRAZYWIFE.COM, SABINA-LEIGH.COM, MYBOOBS.EU, WEDOKI.COM, KASIA-KELLY.COM, BEHIND-THE-PORN.COM, INESCUDNA.EU, ANETABUENA.EU, MAGIC-LEGS.COM, MYGIRLBOOBS.COM,BOOBSAMATEUR.EU,MARYSIA-TAKTAK.COM, CAROLA-COTT.COM, CYNTIA-CYMES.COM, MYBOOBSUNCENSORED.COM, NAUGHTYARABELLA.US,PISSINGHD.COM,TOPWEBMODELS.COM, 2GIRLS1CAMERA.COM, COUGARSEASON.COM, BIGGULPGILRS.COM, DEEPTHROATSIRENS.COM, FACIALSFOREVER.COM, POUNDEDPETITE.COM, SHESBRANDNEW.COM, RED-XXX.COM, SWALLOWED.COM, BANGINGMILF.COM, BUTTMUNCHIN.COM, CREAMPIEHIGH.COM, INTERRACIAL-X.COM, SALADTOSSIN.COM, SLUTTYSTEPDAUGHTER.COM, SLUTTYSTEPMOTHER.COM, SLUTTYSTEPSISTER.COM, POVPERV.COM, TEENGONZO.COM, VRHUSH.COM, HITZEFREI.COM, MYXXXPARADISE.COM, MYBOOBSPARADISE.COM, MYLEGSPARADISE.COM, MYEXGFPARADISE.COM, BUSTYPATSY.COM, KASIAKELLY.COM, ANASSTAZIABOOTY.COM, DORADOLCE.COM, BEHINDSCENEXXX.COM, HITZEFREI.XXX, COUPE-MOVIES.COM, HITZEFREI-MOBIL.DE
We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information
is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate
and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing
and using our Sites. By accessing and using our Sites, you signify
your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with
our information practices, please do not access or use our Sites.
As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion,
to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time
by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective
upon posting.
Information Collection and Use
We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Sites.
We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways
different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect
information from our users at several different points throughout
our Sites.
Registration and Order Forms
In order to gain access to our Site, you may be requested to
provide us with your date of birth. In addition, in order to
purchase goods and services from our Sites, or to become a member of
our Sites, a user must complete the on-line registration/order form.
During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain
contact information (which may include your name, mailing address,
phone number, fax number, and e-mail address). If we have trouble
processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact
information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to
time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional
information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your
needs.
Law Enforcement
We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities,
private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our
end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also
notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our
users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child
pornography.
Links
The Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that
we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our
Sites they should read the privacy statements of each and every web
site that collects personally identifiable
information.
Security
We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the
information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by
using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to
contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security
measures.
Third Party Sources of Information
From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may
supplement the information we receive from you with information we
obtain from third party sources.
Children
We do not collect personally identifiable information from them. We
encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with
their children and to participate in the interactive activities
offered on the sites their children visit.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as
phone number), or if a user no longer desires our service, you may
contact us to correct or update this
information.
Choice/Opt-out
From time to time, we may send our users e-mail or other notices
regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may
be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive
materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by
contacting us.
Notification of Changes
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time
by posting such changes on our Sites. Any changes to this Privacy
Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you
access or use any of our Sites, you are required to periodically
check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access
or use any of our Sites after we have changed our Privacy Policy,
you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy
Policy.
If we decide to use your
personally identifiable information in a manner materially different
from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such
information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such
changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail
address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute
acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice
will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out" so that we may not
use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is
different from the manner described at the time that you provided us
with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out"
pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you
agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in
the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address
for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then
you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be
effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which
shall also disclose information about how you may "opt-out" so that
we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner
which is materially different from the manner described at the time
that you provided us with such information. If you do not
affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within
the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your
personally identifiable information as described in the posted
notice).
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you
otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable
information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide
us with your password, user name and account number so we can
service you quicker.
For any additional information please contact
us.
| Go Back to Home Page |
